

60 Newtown Lawns, Mullingar, Co. Westmeath

085 2155306

davidwbrennan@hotmail.com

https:/www.linkedin.com/in/daithy in

https://github.com/s00172994

daithy.com



## **BIO**

I am a motivated, enthusiastic and creative student currently studying BSc. in Computing in Games Development at Institute of Technology, Sligo. I am working with Unity, MonoGame and GameMaker: Studio and specialise in object-oriented languages, developing in C# and TypeScript with a flair for programming and games development.



## **EDUCATION**

## BSc. in Computing in Games Development (Level 7) | IT Sligo, Sligo

2016 - PRESENT

• 2<sup>nd</sup> Year GPA: 84.16%

• 1st Year GPA: 81.16%

I am currently a **Student Mentor** at IT Sligo 2018 and was **Class Representative** 2016-2017. I actively participate in several societies including **Games Society** and IT Sligo's Badminton team, competing in **Badminton Intervarsities 2017** and **ISBT Limerick 2017**.

I received 2 awards by competing in Games Fleadh 2018.

## **Leaving Certificate | St. Mary's C.B.S. (Coláiste Mhuire), Mullingar** 2010 – 2015

• Final Score: 330 Points

I was nominated **Student of the Year 2015** by my year head.



## **AWARDS**

# Game Studio Ireland Challenge - College Runner Up and Best Windows Platform (UWP) Game | Games Fleadh 2018

**MARCH 2018** 

Both awards received from Prof. Vincent Cunnane (President LIT) and Stephen Howell (Microsoft Ireland).

## Games Development - Year 1 Games Competition Runner Up | IT Sligo

Award received from Games Development lecturers Neil Gannon and Paul Powell.



## **EXPERIENCE**

## **Customer Assistant | Tesco**

AUGUST 2015 - OCTOBER 2016

I developed my skills in a working team environment taking up a year of work at Tesco gaining further insight into the world of business, boosting my interpersonal skills.

## **General Assistant | Mullingar Arts Centre**

2014 - 2016

I have performed various jobs for the Arts Centre over the years.

These included:

- Bartender work
- Reception work
- Ushering
- Front desk cashier work
- Stage lighting
- Stage hand work



## SKILLS

#### Programming Languages:

- Proficient in .NET, C# and TypeScript.
- Adept at data structures, algorithms, problem solving, end-to-end coding.
- Learning C++, JavaScript and Java.

#### Additional Skills:

- LINQ, WPF and ASP.NET.
- Agile Methodologies.
- Unified Modeling Language (UML).
- Skilled in teamwork, leadership, creative thinking.
- Quick to pick up new languages or frameworks.

## **Source Control Tools:**

Git

### **Tool Proficiency:**

- Microsoft Visual Studio
- VS Code
- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe Illustrator
- Audacity
- FL Studio
- Paint.NET
- Maya 3D
- Source SDK



## **PROJECTS**

## Dissonance | C#

MAY 2018 - PRESENT

Project Dissonance is my **final year project** in the 3rd year of my Games Development course, developing in **Unity 3D** and working with **Killing Spraoi**, a team of four highly motivated students from IT Sligo.

## **STEEL WRATH | C#**

NOVEMBER 2017 - MARCH 2018

Steel Wrath features **smooth tank controls**, tank crew **power-ups**, randomized tank spawns and tank types. I also implemented an **A\* path-finding algorithm** in combination with **custom behaviours** for enemy Al tanks. I undertook all roles necessary on my own.

## Cry of Fear Halloween Collaboration (Custom Campaign) Entry | C++

NOVEMBER 2012 – NOVEMBER 2012

At the age of **15**, I participated in the Cry of Fear Halloween Community Collab using Valve's **GoldSrc** engine in November 2012 and worked with community mappers over **Skype** calls.

The custom campaign was played by many, including YouTube personality 'Markiplier'.



### REFERENCES

Sean Lynch

Director

Mullingar Arts Centre

•: 086 6060755

Neil Gannon Games Lecturer IT Sligo neil.gannon@gmail.com Keith McManus

Programming Lecturer
IT Sligo

: 071 91 55465

Sheila McNeely
Former Tesco Manager
Tesco

: 086 367 3335